Student Affairs, Division for; Records ua730
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Athletics Memoranda [2 of 2], 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Athletics, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Athletics, 1997 January (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Athletics, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Athletic Department Funding, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Student Advisory Board Athlete, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Athletics Funding and Hiring Correspondence [1 of 2], 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Athletics Funding and Hiring Correspondence [2 of 2], 1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Change to Division I Athletics Files, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Briefing Paper Div. I, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Great Danes and New York Giants Football Files [1 of 2], 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Great Danes and New York Giants Football Files [2 of 2], 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Department of Intercollegiate Athletics Policies and Procedures Manual, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Department of Athletics Personnel Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Athletic Conference Affiliation Options- Meeting w/ President Hitchcock, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Linda- Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Metro-Atlantic Athletic Conference, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Northeast Conference, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Proposal to Reclassify NCAA Division II Membership to Division I to the University Senate, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Reports and Handbooks, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Patriot League, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Athletics Yearbook and University Viewbooks, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- IAAB, 1989-1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- President Hitchcock's Open Meetings, 1999 October; 1999 December (Box 16, Folder 18)
- President's Open Meetings Notes Academic Year, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Speeches, 1963 June (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Colgate, 1963 August; 1963 September (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Speeches- Meetings, 1952-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Salary Materials, 1950-1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- SLS, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- P1QU Summaries, 1949-1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Kappa Beta Fraternity, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Fraternity- Old, 1956-1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Sorority, 1954-1967 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Publications, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Dean Hartley Sorority- Freternity Report, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Rivalry, 1962 May (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Speech Days, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Student Activities, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Student Activities, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Fraternity- Recent, 1952-1962 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Fraternity Scholarship, 1939-1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Theta XI Omega, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- College Ambassador, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Dippikill Camp, 1959-1963 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Frosh Weekend, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Leadership Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Moving Up Day, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Dr. Hartley- Personal, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Correspondence A-G, 1952-1960 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Correspondence H-O, 1953-1962 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Correspondence P-Z, 1952-1958 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Correspondence State Colleges, 1952-1960 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- State Universities (by university), 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Dead Stokes… Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Police Matters, 1962 January (Box 17, Folder 31)
- "University, 1970", 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- National Defense Loans, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- N.Y.S.H.F.A.C., 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- (Room + Board) Short-Term Loans Outstanding Bills, 1963 February (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Tuition, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Student Personnel Program, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Suggested Readings- Res Hall Personnel, Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Faculty- Student Assn. Directors Meetings, 1961 July (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Faculty- Student Assoc., 1956 October; 1963 January (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Food Service, 1954-1963 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Residence Hall Counselors Preparations Program, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Residence Assistants, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Loan Applications Alumni Association, Undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Student Cosun. Com., 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Students (Confidential Reports), 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Student Personnel Services, Undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Organization and Responsibility, 1963 July (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Staff Mtgs, 1953 March; 1963 June (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Student Personnel Staff Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Alumni Association, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Committee On Counseling Programs (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Committees-I, Undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Committee On Student Activities, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Faculties Association, 1962 October (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Residence Hall Directors Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- The Student Personnel Program, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Student Union, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Memoranda To Residence Hall Directors and Other Staff Members, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- OTS S-A Scores Classes 26-31, Undated (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Student Personal History Form, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Historical Interest (College), 1949-1962 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Orientations, 1949-1962 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Arbitration, Undated (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Association of College Unions, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Insurance- Student, 1952-1959 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Honor System, 1944-1950 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Regulations Student, 1944-1964 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Myskania, Undated (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Faculty Questionnaire Rating Scale, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Orientation Skills, Undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Orientation Study, Undated (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Transfers- Rating Scale, Undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Class Lists, 1930-1937 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Class Rosters *Follow Up, 1930-1938; 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Five-Year Plan, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Committees: EOP Advisory, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- First Progress Report, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Financial Report Procedures, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Memoranda to Students, 1973-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Judicial Committee, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Sorority Scholarship Cup, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Leadership Conference, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Finances, 1957-1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Introduction to College, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- New Residence Halls, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Student Personnel Office, 1953-1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Student Affairs, 1984-1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Student Affairs, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- ROTC Air Force, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Office of Student Affairs, 1977-1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Orientation Corrdination Committee Student Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Student Affairs Sex Education & Drugs Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Five Year Plan Progress Report, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Student Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Departmental Memoranda, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Judicial Advisors Manual, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Division's Five Year Plan, 1986 June (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Student Guidelines, 1964-1984 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Judicial Affairs, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Student Affairs Council, 1992-1996 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Safety, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Satiafa, 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- President Hitchcock Correspondence [1 of 4], 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- President Hitchcock Correspondence [2 of 4], 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- President Hitchcock Correspondence [3 of 4], 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- President Hitchcock Correspondence [4 of 4], 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)